sportchek.ca 2011-05-05

# Sport Chek - Help Desk - Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment to You

At SportChek.ca, the protection of your personal information is a top priority. This Privacy Policy is intended to assist you to understand the type of information that we gather about you when you visit or contact us about SportChek.ca, how we use that information and the safeguards that we have in place to protect your information. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information collected online at SportChek.ca. By visiting SportChek.ca, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## About SportChek.ca

SportChek.ca is owned and operated by Sport-Chek International 2000 Ltd., a wholly-owned subsidiary of The Forzani Group Ltd. (collectively referred to herein as "SportChek.ca", "we" or "us"). This site may, from time to time, contain links to other sites. Although we make every effort to ensure that such links are from reputable sources that respect your privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites and we encourage you to read their privacy policies before submitting any personal information.

We have also included in this Privacy Policy details about how we collect, use and protect the information you decide to provide to us. This Privacy Policy will tell you:

  1. What kind of information is collected during your use of the SportChek.ca site;
  2. How we use this information;
  3. How we may share this information; 
  4. How we protect your information;
  5. How we handle cookies; and
  6. How you may contact our privacy officer with any concerns.

Kindly take note that we may change or add to this Privacy Policy at any time without notice so we encourage you to review it periodically. SportChek.ca reserves the right to vary this policy by province as required by law.

## 1\. What Information Do We Collect?

In accordance with the relevant privacy legislation in Canada, we limit our collection of personal information to those details necessary to complete the relevant transaction with you. Your knowledge and consent (which may be given expressly or impliedly by your conduct) are required for the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information.

SportChek.ca may ask you to provide personal information in the following circumstances:

Online shopping: when you establish or update an account or make a purchase online you will be asked for certain information in order for us to process your request;

Membership & Accounts: when you become a member of SportChek.ca you will be asked to set up an account which will contain certain information about you; 

Contests & Surveys: in order to properly administer our contests and select a valid winner, we require certain personal information to be provided. Similarly, we require some basic information upon the completion of a survey to verify the results;

Information submitted: when you submit things such as product reviews, stories, related photos or video; 

Contact us: any time you contact our customer service department your name, contact information and details regarding your issue are logged;

Wish Lists/Tell-a-Friend: you have the ability to create a wish list on SportChek.ca and send it to a friend, and to send a product description or site information to a friend. You will be prompted to enter your name and email address and your friend's name and email address;

Shop by Appointment: at SportChek.ca we strive to make your shopping experience as unique and meaningful as possible. We are proud to offer the ability for you to set up a time to meet with one of our knowledgeable sales associates about select products in our land based stores. You will be asked to enter contact information so that we may contact you to set up a mutually agreeable time and location; and

Promotions: you may register to receive information about our special promotions without becoming a SportChek.ca member. You will be asked to enter your email address.

Team Registration: when you register your team with Team Assist you will be asked for certain personal information in order for us to complete the registration, set up your team profile, track your team's purchases, update you and your team about the Team Assist program, and provide you with status updates.

Categories of information collected online may include name, billing and shipping address, email address, phone numbers, credit card information, gift card information, demographic information, your photo or video, stories or personal reviews or experiences that you share.

Categories of information collected for the Team Assist program may include team name, team's sport and level, team's demographic information, team contact's name, team contact's position with team, and team contact's mailing address, phone numbers and email address.

## 2\. How Do We Use The Information That We Collect?

At SportChek.ca we use the personal information that we collect from you only for the purposes outlined to you upon collection.

Your personal information may be used by SportChek.ca, its agents and service providers:

Administration: to administer and enhance your guest and / or customer relationship with us, including to administer accounts, maintain wish lists, facilitate deliveries, administer our customer service centre, make and receive payments and fulfill contractual obligations;

Customer Needs: to understand your needs and preferences and respond to your requests which will allow us to tailor our offerings to you. This may include use for statistical analysis;

Communication: to communicate with you about products, services, special offerings and events or programs offered by SportChek.ca or its marketing partners that may be of interest to you; 

Promotions: to conduct surveys, contests and promotions;

Inappropriate Behavior: to detect and protect SportChek.ca and other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, theft, fraud and other illegal activity;

Legal and Corporate use: to comply with SportChek.ca audit requirements and to audit compliance with laws, SportChek.ca corporate policies, procedures and contractual obligations. We may also use this information to respond to all administrative and legal proceedings or to protect our rights, property or safety of the Company, affiliates, service providers, customers or otherwise; and

Other: for any other purpose for which you consent.

We will not retain your personal information any longer than is required to fulfill the business purpose for which you provided the information or as required by law. Further, only those employees or third parties who require your personal information in the performance of their duties will have access to your personal information. 

Your information will be processed and stored in the GSI servers located in Virginia and New Jersey. Certain information will also be held at the head office of Sport-Chek International 2000 Ltd. located at 824, 41st Avenue NE, Calgary, Alberta. Information used by the third party who will conduct email promotions and campaigns will be stored in Waltham, MA and Dallas, TX. Information used by the third parties who will administer the Team Assist program will be stored in Toronto, ON and Montreal, QC. Where personal information is stored or processed outside of Canada, it is subject to the laws of that foreign jurisdiction and may be accessible to that jurisdiction's governments, courts, law enforcement and regulatory agencies.

## 3\. How Will We Share The Information That We Collect?

We do not license, sell or provide your personal information to any third party unless required or permitted by law. We do however have relationships with trusted third parties to better serve our customers. These relationships include:

Web store operations: GSI fulfills the retail operation component of SportChek.ca pursuant to an agreement with us. GSI is authorized to use personal information collected through these services in connection with the services they are engaged to perform;

Affiliates: from time to time we may establish an affiliate program whereby other web sites earn money by linking customers to SportChek.ca from their sites. Although these affiliates can access data about the number of transactions resulting from a link, they can not access our customers' personal information;

Order fulfillment: GSI and certain other vendors may provide customer order fulfillment, customer service and shipping services. They will have access to only that information necessary to fulfill and ship the orders through such vendors;

Credit Card Processing: we use Chase Paymentech Solutions, LLC to process credit card information entered by a customer on SportChek.ca. We supply them with data for credit card authorization and fraud detection only and they are restricted from using the data for any other purpose;

Marketing and Promotions: we may engage certain parties to assist in the dissemination of marketing and promotional offers to existing customers or members of SportChek.ca who have agreed to accept such promotional material; and

Additional relationship: SportChek.ca or GSI may engage other third parties to assist in such services as fulfillment, shipping, customer service, product customization, user reviews, gift cards, order processing, fraud protection and data services. These parties will only have that information necessary and will be restricted in their use of such information, whether contractually or otherwise, to those purposes identified by GSI or SportChek.ca.

When we use trusted third parties to act on our behalf for the purposes outlined herein, we use contractual or other appropriate means to ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy and applicable privacy legislation. 

There is a possibility that Sport-Chek International 2000 Ltd. could amalgamate with, acquire or be acquired by another business entity. If this occurs, some or all of the personal information collected about you will be shared with this entity as well as retained by Sport-Chek International 2000 Ltd.

## 4\. How Do We Protect Your Information?

We realize that our customers are entrusting their personal information to us. This trust is of the utmost importance to us. We maintain several safeguards to ensure that, to the best of our abilities, your information is protected. Some of these measures include restricted access, passwords, encryption, and employee training consistent with industry standard security measures. 

Unfortunately, as with all internet use, despite our efforts there is always the risk that a third party may unlawfully intercept transmissions. As a result, we cannot ensure the complete security of any information you transmit and you transmit all information at your own risk.

## 5\. How Do We Handle Cookies?

SportChek.ca uses cookies to better understand user behavior and to continually enhance the user experience at SportChek.ca. Your web browser temporarily stores a small piece of information called a cookie on your hard drive. SportChek.ca uses the cookie to recall information you gave us so you do not have to provide it each time you visit SportChek.ca. You may disable this function on your personal browser at your discretion.

## 6\. Our Privacy Officer

If you are a registered user you may update your account, including your preferences for receiving promotional materials, at any time by logging into your account. Further, if you are not a registered user but wish to unsubscribe to any future correspondence please click "unsubscribe" at the bottom of any page of the SportChek.ca website.

Your feedback and questions are of the utmost importance to us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices generally, to correct any personal information that we may have about you or wish to opt out of receiving communications from us you may contact us directly at

Privacy Officer  
Sport-Chek International 2000 Ltd.  
824 41st Avenue NE  
Calgary, AB  
T2E 3R3  
Fax: (403) 717 1490

Or at [privacy@forzani.com](mailto:privacy@forzani.com)
